lookin.at 2013-08-21

# Sitelutions - Solutions for your site. All in one place.

Sitelutions (with primary web address of [www.sitelutions.com](http://www.sitelutions.com/)) is wholly owned and operated by InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc., with an address of 4 Bridge Plaza Drive, Englishtown, NJ 07726. All references to "Sitelutions" are actually references to InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc.. All references to "Sitelutions staff" are actually references to employees (part-time, full-time, or subcontractors/1099) of InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc..

This privacy statement covers the site [ www.sitelutions.com](http://www.sitelutions.com/). Because Sitelutions wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users’ privacy, we have agreed to disclose our information practices in order to assure our users that their information **will be kept private and secure.** This privacy statement will address the following items:

  1. What personally identifiable information Sitelutions collects.
  2. What personally identifiable information third parties collect through the Web site.
  3. What organization collects the information.
  4. How Sitelutions uses the information.
  5. With whom Sitelutions may share user information.
  6. What choices are available to users regarding collection, use and distribution of the information.
  7. What types of security procedures are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Sitelutions control.
  8. How users can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact Sitleutions Privacy Department by e-mail [privacy@sitelutions.com](mailto:privacy@sitelutions.com) at (703) 485-4600, or by postal mail at: Sitelutions c/o InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc., 4 Bridge Plaza Drive, Englishtown, NJ 07726.

InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected by Sitelutions. Sitelutions collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

## Registration

In order to use Sitelutions' services, a user must first complete the registration form. During registration a user is required to give contact information (such as name, email address, gender, and geographic location) as well as unique identifiers, such as a username and password.. We use this information to contact the user about services on our site for which he has expressed interest. At times, we may request other optional information, such as annual household income, information on hobbies & interests, etc.. While this is optional, users are encouraged to provide the information so we can provide a more personalized experience on our site. We also may request, at our discretion, a fax or mailed copy of a valid identification document, such as driver's license or passport in order to provide certain advanced services for our users. 

## Order

We request information from the user on our order form. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and physical address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). This information is used for billing purposes and to fill customer’s orders. If we have trouble processing an order, the information is used to contact the user.

## Profile

We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and/or third parties to create a profile of our users. A profile is stored information that we keep on individual users that details their viewing preferences. Consequently, collected information is tied to the users personally identifiable information to provide offers and improve the content of the site for the user. This profile is used to tailor a user’s visit to our Web site, and to direct pertinent marketing promotions to them. Your profile is not shared with other parties, however it may be used to provide anonymous statistics (ie. "We have over 20,000 users in the United States.") to Sitelutions staff or third parties.

## Cookies

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user’s computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies, and may use persistent cookies for advertising, to store your e-mail address (so that we may fill in the login form automatically), or other purposes. For the session ID cookie, once users close the browser, the cookie simply terminates. A persistent cookie is a small text file stored on the user’s hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies can be removed by following Internet browser help file directions. Please take a look at <http://www.cookiecentral.com/> for more information on cookies.

By setting a cookie on our site, users would not have to log in a password more than once, thereby saving time while on our site. If users reject the cookie, they may not login to our site. Therefore, in order to make use of our services, users must accept cookies. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. See the “Profile” section.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. 

## Third Party Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by our Web advertising partners. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not user name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. Rest assured that no personal information is provided to these third-party companies. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Sitelutions only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

## Log Files

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)

We and our third party advertising companies employ a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. The main difference between the two is that clear gifs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear gifs may be tied to a user's account, but are completely secure and cannot and will not be used to disclose information about a user or a user's account to any third parties.

Clear Gifs can "work with" existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same Web site or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company's clear gif, the Web site would match the clear gif's identifier and the advertising company's cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information would then be given to the advertising company. 

In addition, we may use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by the recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If users would like to opt-out of these emails, please see the Opt-out section. 

## Newsletter, Service Announcements, Special Offers and Updates

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify that the user has provided the correct e-mail address. Established members will occasionally (no more than twice per month) receive information on third-party products, services, special deals, and a newsletter. Typically, these offers are combined with a newsletter to provide our users with updates on our products. Because of this, we currently do not offer a way to opt out of these offers without terminating your Sitelutions account. 

## Customer Service

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account we reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes.

## Legal Disclaimer

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site. This includes cases of SPAM and other cases of bad "netiquette."

## Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This allows advertisers to decide whether or not our user base is a good target for their advertising campaign. This is not linked to any personally identifiable information.

## Third Party Advertisers

Our third party advertising companies may share Web site usage information about users with a reputable third party for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site and other sites. For example, our advertising companies use cookies and clear GIFs on this site, which allow them to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site. The information they collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable.

## Third Party Intermediaries

We accept payments via PayPal ( [www.paypal.com](http://www.paypal.com/) ), a well-known, secure payment service owned by e-Bay. We may pre-populate PayPal signup forms when our users make payments through PayPal. PayPal keeps information safe and secure. For information on their privacy policies, go to: <http://www.paypal.com/cgi-bin/webscr?cmd=p/gen/privacy-outside>.

## Service Providers

We partner with other third parties, such as DotRegistrar.com, to provide top-level domain registration services. When the user registers a top-level domain name through Sitelutions, we share names, or other contact information, as well as technical information, such as the user's choice of domain name server addresses with DotRegistrar. This information is necessary for the third party to provide these services. DotRegistrar is not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. DotRegister may continue to provide services to Sitelutions' users should Sitelutions ever become unable to do so. This includes contacting our users with information on how to renew domain names and register additional domain names.

## Business Transitions

In the event that Sitelutions or InfoRelay Online Systems, Inc. goes through a business transition, such as a merger, being acquired by another company, or selling a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred. 

## Choice/Opt-out

Our users are given the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. In order to opt-out, users must terminate their Sitelutions account completely. This may be done by logging in to your Sitelutions account and clicking "delete account."

## Links

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Sitelutions, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site and not information collected by our partners, affiliates, or co-branded resellers.

## Surveys & Contests

From time-to-time our site requests information from users via surveys or contests. Participation in these surveys or contests is completely voluntary and the user therefore has a choice whether or not to disclose this information. The requested information typically includes contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code). Contact information will be used [shared with the contest [survey] sponsors] to notify the winners and award prizes. Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site. Users’ personally identifiable information is not shared with third parties unless we give prior notice and choice. Though we may use an intermediary to conduct these surveys or contests, they may not use users’ personally identifiable information for any secondary purposes. 

## Tell-A-Friend

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the friend’s name and email address. Sitelutions will automatically send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the site. Sitelutions stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email and tracking the success of our referral program. The friend may contact Sitelutions at [privacy@sitelutions.com](mailto:privacy@sitelutions.com) to request the removal of this information from our database.

## Chat Rooms, Message Boards, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users’ information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration/order form asks users to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the best encryption software in the industry - SSL. While on a secure page, such as our order form, the lock icon on the bottom of Web browsers such as Netscape Navigator and Microsoft Internet Explorer becomes locked, as opposed to un-locked, or open, when users are just ‘surfing’. To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.rsasecurity.com/rsalabs/faq/5-1-2.html>.

While we use SSL encryption to protect sensitive information online, we also do everything in our power to protect user-information off-line. All of our users’ information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, our billing clerk or a customer service representative) are granted access to personally identifiable information. Our employees must use password-protected screen-savers when they leave their desk. When they return, they must re-enter their password to re-gain access to user information. Furthermore, ALL employees are kept up-to-date on our security and privacy practices. Any time new policies are added, our employees are notified and/or reminded about the importance we place on privacy, and what they can do to ensure our users’ information is protected. Finally, the servers that store personally identifiable information are in a secure environment, in a locked facility. For more information on security and why our site is secure, view ourSecurity Statement.

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [info@sitelutions.com](mailto:info@sitelutions.com).

## Supplementation of Information 

In order for this Web site to properly fulfill its obligation to users it is necessary for us to supplement the information we receive with information from 3rd party sources.

## ID & Address Verification

We may in some cases request fax or postal mail delivered copies of a users'identification. This may be done for various reasons, and is common practice for our users that request shell accounts (direct SSH access to our servers).

## Domain Name Registration

We use the database of our partner, DotRegistrar.com, to check domain name availability. When a users checks to see if a domain is available through our site, DotRegistrar provides us with the necessary availability information. We also interface with the central WHOIS database directly for domain information.

## Enhancement of Marketing Profile

We purchase third party marketing data and add it to our existing user database to better target our advertising and provide pertinent offers we think our users would be interested in. We use this information to enhance or overlay the ‘profile’ of individual users. This aggregate marketing data is therefore tied to the users’ personally identifiable information. See also the “Profile.”

## Correcting/Updating/Deleting/Deactivating Personal Information

If a user’s personally identifiable information changes (such as zip code, phone, email or postal address), or if a user no longer desires our service, we provide a way to correct, update or delete/deactivate users’ personally identifiable information. This can usually be done by logging into your Sitelutions account and clicking the "Edit User Profile" link. 

## Notification of Changes

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If, however, we are going to use users’ personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by posting a notice on our Web site for 30 days.

If users have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:

Phone: (703) 485-4600   
Fax: (703) 485-4600   
Email: [privacy@sitelutions.com](mailto:privacy@sitelutions.com)  
Postal Address: 22900 Shaw Rd. Suite 112-5, Sterling, VA 20166, USA   
Web site URL: http://www.sitelutions.com/
